{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Basement Drain Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/40446/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40446,"taskName":"Basement Drainage Channels - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair Basement Surface Drainage Channels","xmTaskDescriptor":"Basement Drain Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1402,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Basement Drainage Channels flooding surface","textMessagingName":"Repr Drain Channels","rolloverLongDesc":"Less expensive, less disruptive alternative to buried floor drains. Holes are drilled into walls just above the floor line to allow water to drain out. Plastic channels are glued to the wall/floor joint. The channels direct the water to floor drains or a sump pump.","rolloverShortDesc":"Plastic channels mounted where floor meets wall.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Basement Surface Drainage Channels.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Basement Drain Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fix Basement Drainage System","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":47,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Basement Drainage Channels Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Basement Drainage Channels - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Basement Drainage Channel Project","urlName":"Basement-Drainage-Channels-Repair","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Basement Drain Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Basement,Drainage,Channels,flooding,surface,foundation,drain, irrigation, moisture, mildew, mold","emcCategoryOid":-12033,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":737,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40446/":{"taskOID":40446,"originalTaskOID":40446,"setID":737,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4595,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Channels","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of interior channels need repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4719,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Plastic channels behind baseboard","answerDisplayText":"Plastic channels behind baseboard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1359,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Channels dug into concrete slab","answerDisplayText":"Channels dug into concrete slab","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1676,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Covered channels buried in slab","answerDisplayText":"Covered channels buried in slab","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4596,"questionDisplayText":"Problem Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the problem?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1357,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Channels can't handle water volume","answerDisplayText":"Channels can't handle water volume","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1360,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Channels not sloped properly to drain","answerDisplayText":"Channels not sloped properly to drain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1358,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Channels drain to faulty sump pump","answerDisplayText":"Channels drain to faulty sump pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1356,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Channels are clogged","answerDisplayText":"Channels are clogged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":934,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Bad odors","answerDisplayText":"Bad odors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2775,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Requires cleaning/maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Requires cleaning/maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4595,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Channels","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of interior channels need repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4719,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Plastic channels behind baseboard","answerDisplayText":"Plastic channels behind baseboard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1359,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Channels dug into concrete slab","answerDisplayText":"Channels dug into concrete slab","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1676,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Covered channels buried in slab","answerDisplayText":"Covered channels buried in slab","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4719,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Plastic channels behind baseboard","answerDisplayText":"Plastic channels behind baseboard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1359,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Channels dug into concrete slab","answerDisplayText":"Channels dug into concrete slab","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1676,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Covered channels buried in slab","answerDisplayText":"Covered channels buried in slab","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4596,"questionDisplayText":"Problem Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the problem?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1357,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Channels can't handle water volume","answerDisplayText":"Channels can't handle water volume","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1360,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Channels not sloped properly to drain","answerDisplayText":"Channels not sloped properly to drain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1358,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Channels drain to faulty sump pump","answerDisplayText":"Channels drain to faulty sump pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1356,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Channels are clogged","answerDisplayText":"Channels are clogged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":934,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Bad odors","answerDisplayText":"Bad odors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2775,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Requires cleaning/maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Requires cleaning/maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1357,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Channels can't handle water volume","answerDisplayText":"Channels can't handle water volume","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1360,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Channels not sloped properly to drain","answerDisplayText":"Channels not sloped properly to drain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1358,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Channels drain to faulty sump pump","answerDisplayText":"Channels drain to faulty sump pump","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1356,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Channels are clogged","answerDisplayText":"Channels are clogged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":934,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Bad odors","answerDisplayText":"Bad odors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2775,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Requires cleaning/maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Requires cleaning/maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}